This temple was built around the time Ancient Kyoto was established,
and was originally called Takaosan-ji Temple.
Residing here was Kobo Daishi, Kukai.
which led to the temple being officially named Jingo-kokuso-shingon -ji.
The true magnificence of this Jingo-ji Temple really hits you when come here.
It was a place I'd long yearned to visit.
The opportunity to perform here thanks to my connection with Taro,
and the chance to experience this truly special moment,
has been an incredibly significant experience for me.
Taro-san makes such a wonderful painting.
While the painting itself is very wild,
the temple that left such a impression on Taro's mind
he's been visiting here for a long time, and that sparked his inspiration for the painting.
So when I suggested, "Wouldn't it be nice to write some calligraphy too?
he said, "Please join in,
and that's how I came to participate this time.
This painting features a wolf or a fox-like figure, incredibly powerful
This great piece is such a wild, powerful painting.
So, conversely I thought about stillness.
About quiet observation. About gazing quietly.
When he was painting, the people around him were truly quiet,
They were intently watching the music and Taro's brushwork.
Well, (it means) by quietly observing
you sort out your own heart and rediscover your true self.
I felt that opportunity was born this time,
so I was inspired to write those characters.
It's an amazing sensation.
the moment when a groove is born.
That moment when each element seems to blend together.
That experience is incredibly fascinating.
I'm looking forward to discovering how the sound changes in other places.
After Taro painted,
It was a true honor to be able to add my calligraphy
It was truly wonderful, with the flute, guitar, and piano being played all around us.
As it matched the music so perfectly,
I said, "If there's another chance like this, I'd love to collaborate again.
I'm incredibly happy to have been part of such a performance.
An experience like this doesn't come along often in life, and it made truely happy.
I'm also incredibly proud that Chief Priest Taniuchi participated.
It's not something you can easily ask for, and it's not something you experience often, even as an artist.
learned a lot from the priest too
While deeply feeling the spirit of Kyoto
I was overjoyed to do live art right here in front of The Deity of Protection.